Héctor Haro Hermosillo

IT AND WEB SPECIALIST



PROFILE

Phone

341-160-0351

Address

General Neri 86 A Teocuitatlan de Corona, Jal

Email

hector8.haro@gmail.com

Website

https://hectorharohermosilloweb.vercel.app

OBJECTIVE

Pursuing a technology-oriented position utilizing my software/hardware based skills. I aim to bring in results and innovation by leveraging multi-platform troubleshooting skills, and experience in both close-knit and enterprise environments. Capable of excelling independently or within a team I will proudly produce many projects that will extend the potential of any business/organization.

SKILLS



JavaScript



React



HTML



CSS



















EXPERIENCE

(2016 - 2018)

Jr. JavasScript Developer at Software Allies.

Development and maintenance of FrontEnd functionality.

Development prototypes for applications and websites. Creation logos, banners and buttons for the sites.

(2018 - 2021)

IT Consultant of the City Hall of Teocuitatlan de Corona. Development, implementation and maintenance of the website for the town.

(2021 - Now)

React developer (Freelancer), development from scratch website for a couple of personal projects.

- * PizzaApp
- * CoffeApp

EDUCATION

Telematic Engineering UdG, CUSur 2012-2017 Gained experience and additional knowledge in PHP, HTML, CSS, JS

LANGUAGES

Spanish

English B2 Advanced Proulex PDU

CERTIFICATES

*Javascript School

https://platzi.com/@hector-haro-hermosillo/ Código: 0597cc10-d6bd-4d47-912a-d67c58670d98

*React JS

https://platzi.com/@hector-haro-hermosillo/ Código: 3229bf81-c5e9-4396-b1aa-8d1e25b84705

*FrontEnd Developer

https://platzi.com/@hector-haro-hermosillo/ Código: 8d0df871-73ae-4566-b4bb-85dc0f04eaae

*BackEnd con Node

https://platzi.com/@hector-haro-hermosillo/ Código: d77bc84f-a4c3-41a5-b663-caf92f32adce